Haris Mahmood

Android Developer

Firdous Market, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan. +92 3410865458 mahmoodharis88@gmail.com

Objective:

My aim is to be a part of high-end software industry by providing quality services to the clients. Work with an organization that gives an opportunity to exhibit my skills of programming and development, where I could get professional expertise and considerable knowledge, with hard work, perseverance and dedication.

Education:

BS (Software Engineering) 2014 - 2018
COMSATS University Islamabad CGPA: 3.12

ICS 2012 - 2014

Covernment Degree College Jahanian 73 63%

Government Degree College Jahanian 72.63%

Matric2010 - 2012Government Model High School, Jahanian79.33%

(B.I.S.E Multan)

Work Experience:

Job Description: Job - (1st March 2021 - On Going)

Company: Terafort

Work Type: Mobile App Development

Tech Stack: Java, Kotlin

Job Description: Job - (16 June 2020 – March 2021)

Company: B4U Cabs

Work Type: Mobile App Development

Tech Stack: Java, Kotlin

Job Description: Job - (1st March 2019 – 15 June 2020)

Company: Elastic Brainz Technologies **Work Type:** Mobile App Development

Tech Stack: Java, Kotlin

Job Description: Job - (1st January 2018 –28 February 2019)

Company: Codiro Technologies

Work Type: Mobile App Development

Tech Stack: Java

Job Description: Internship - (1st June 2017 – 31August 2018)

Company: MEPCO

Work Type: Mobile App Development

Tech Stack: Java

Project Name: B4U Cabs

Combine all your safety, personnel, and operations paperwork into a single cloud-based platform, all run by an easy-to-use and accessible mobile app. Say goodbye to confusing paperwork and thick binders.

Project Name: B4U Cabs

The state-of-the-art tracking system ensures the safety of B4U Cabs customers. B4U Cabs put luxury cars, economical Rickshaws and delivery bikes all under your tap approach. B4U Cabs Pakistan is offering low rates from market on all rides.

Project Name: B4U Boss

B4U BOSS is an app for car drivers to get rides its a service provided by the B4U. Users can get rides and earn money.

Project Name: Formee

- Free: Post your Classified Ads for free and start selling your products online by just taking a photo from your phone.
- Food Scanner: The Formee food scanner let you scan shelf products of Aldi, Costco and Woolworths for Halal, Vegan or Kosher certification.
- Organized: Search product listings from over 50 categories and you can use our advanced search & filter to reach your desired results.
- Employment: By using Formee, you can look for new job postings in nearby Location or post a job to find in nearby location.
- School Finder: Lets you search and find suitable schools/classes near your location for your children
- Other modules like Handyman, Wellbeing, Spa, Fitness, Event, Restaurant, Cinema, Beauty, Sport Tickets, Tourism.

Project Name: BrandFace

BrandFace has developed a video sharing platform to help brands reach authentic and co-created video content that can be used and re-used across all marketing channels to enhance engagement with new generation as well as to boost sales.

Project Name: Rabbta IJT

Social app for IJT members where they can create any post, questions, survey and create polls as well. Other members can comment on post, answer the question, fill the survey and vote polls.

Project Name: Allied Contractors

Application that can will manage the attendance and salaries of the employees in an organization. Admin can create departments and add employees in that department. Employee can view his salaries and attendance.

Project Name: Aquapura

Android app develop for water supplying company in which manager can check sales of every agent, supplier and customers and agent can sale products and generate receipt using Bluetooth printer.

Project Name: Android Code Generator

Android application that provide UI to design your database schema(database, tables, fields and relationships), then use the built-in generator to get the corresponding code. This generated code consists of three Java classes which create database using content provider. User just have to paste that code in his project.

Hobbies:

▶ Computer Games

References:

▶ Will be provided on demand.